Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Slides Series, circa 1887-2005 and undated, (13 boxes)
  - Clients
    - International Ads
      - Portugal (Lisbon)
        - Beirsdorf (outdoor) (1 slide), 1988 May-Aug. (Box SL7)
        - Copaz (2 slides), 1988 May-Aug. (Box SL7)
        - CTT-Int. Serv. (6 slides), 1988 May-Aug. (Box SL7)
        - Edipress (5 slides), 1988 May-Aug. (Box SL7)
        - M.H. Bank (4 slides), 1988 May-Aug. (Box SL7)
        - Montepio Geral (1 slide), 1988 May-Aug. (Box SL7)
      - Puerto Rico
        - Pan Am (2 slides), undated (Box SL7)
      - Peru (Lima)
        - Miscellaneous (8 slides), undated (Box SL7)
      - Spain
        - General
          - Barcelona (1 slide #82), 1984 (Box SL7)
          - Kraft (1 slide), undated (Box SL7)
          - Pan Am (2 slides), undated (Box SL7)
          - Winston (9 slides), circa 1984 (Box SL7)
          - Miscellaneous (7 slides), 1988 (Box SL7)
        - Madrid
          - Beefeater (1 slide #M-9), 1984 (Box SL7)
          - Bacardi (6 slides #19,20,21,22,M-6,M-7), 1983-1984 (Box SL7)
          - DeBeers/Men (5 slides #7,8,9,10,Extra), 1982-1983 (Box SL7)
          - Fisher-Price (3 slides #16,17,18), 1983 (Box SL7)
          - Ford (1 slide #M-2), 1984 (Box SL7)
          - Metro (6 slides #1,2,3,4,5,6), 1983 (Box SL7)
          - Pirelli Tires (5 slides #11,12,13,14,15), 1983 (Box SL7)
          - Quorum (1 slide #B-4), 1984 (Box SL7)
          - Ripolin Express (2 slides), 1972 (Box SL7)
      - Sweden
        - Ford (1 slide), undated (Box SL7)
        - Klimgers (1 slide), undated (Box SL7)
        - Seagrams (1 slide), 1984 (Box SL7)
      - Switzerland
        - Martini (1 slide), 1972 (Box SL7)
      - Uruguay (served by Caracas office)
        - General (3 slides), circa 1984 (Box SL7)
        - Aster (1 slide), 1984 (Box SL7)
        - Ford (2 slides), 1984 (Box SL7)
        - Globero Adams (2 slides), 1984 (Box SL7)
        - Johnson (1 slide), 1984 (Box SL7)
      - Venezuela (Caracas)
        - Kelloggs (2 slides), undated (Box SL7)
        - Nabisco (3 slides), circa 1984 (Box SL7)
        - Pan Am (14 slides), undated (Box SL7)
        - Quaker Oats (2 slides), undated (Box SL7)
      - Multinational campaigns
        - Kodak (34 slides), circa 1963 and undated (Box SL7)
        - Ford (3 slides), undated (Box SL7)
  - Offices
    - Domestic
      - Chicago (1 slide #40), undated (Box SL8)
        - Awards party
          - Ben Gilmore (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Dave Devasy, Sandy Stern, John Scott (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Joyce Saxon (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Mary Pat Hutton (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Mike Kalasunas (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Pat O'Kara (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Ron Rasoletti, Louise Sandes (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Shari Wall (1 slide), 1983 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Alan Webb, Tom DeMint (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Jack Tukey, Thorn Wierum (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - John Furr, Marion Howington, Alan Webb (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Marion Howington (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Marion Howington, Bruce Beach (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
        - Awards show
          - John Scott,Tom Hall (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Mike Kalasunas,Bob Irvine (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
          - Thorn Wierum (1 slide), 1984 Dec. (Box SL8)
        - John Hancock Center (2 slides), undated (Box SL8)
        - Kitchen (3 slides), circa 1924 (Box SL8)
        - Summer party
          - General (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
          - Alan Webb (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
          - Bill Hooe, Tom Demint, Peggy Pilas (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
          - Bill Reishtein, Ron Rasollet (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
          - Gary Moss, George Lange (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
          - Tom Hall (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
          - Warm up for run (1 slide), 1984 June (Box SL8)
        - Tacoma Building (1 slide), circa 1891 (Box SL8)
        - The Rookery (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
        - Thompson Cup (18 slides), 2005 June (Box SL8)
        - Wrigley Building (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - Detroit-Dearborn (16 slides), undated (Box SL8)
      - Hollywood (1 slide), 1936-1937 (Box SL8)
      - Los Angeles (4 slides), undated (Box SL8)
      - Miami (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - New York
        - 38 Park (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
        - 466 Lexington (12 slides), 1981 and undated (Box SL8)
        - Graybar (56 slides), 1960s (Box SL8)
        - Miscellaneous office images (70 slides), 1906-1960s (Box SL8)
      - San Francisco, undated (Box SL8)
      - Washington D.C. (3 slides), undated (Box SL8)
    - International
      - Argentina (2 slides), undated (Box SL8)
      - Australia-Melboune Office (1 slide #170A), undated (Box SL8)
      - Australia-Perth Office, undated (Box SL8)
      - Australia-Sydney Office (3 slides #170, 221), undated (Box SL8)
      - Austria-Vienna Office (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - Africa (1 slide #198), undated (Box SL8)
      - Brazil--Rio de Janeiro, undated (Box SL8)
      - Brazil--São Paulo, undated (Box SL8)
      - Canada-Vancouver (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - Chile--Santiago, undated (Box SL8)
      - Colombia--Bogota, undated (Box SL8)
      - Denmark-Copenhagen (1 slide #42), undated (Box SL8)
      - Dubai, undated (Box SL8)
      - Ecuador--Guayaquil, undated (Box SL8)
      - Ecuador--Quito, undated (Box SL8)
      - Finland--Helsinki, undated (Box SL8)
      - France (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - France--Lyon, undated (Box SL8)
      - France-Paris (2 slides), circa 1949 (Box SL8)
      - Germany--Dusseldorf, undated (Box SL8)
      - Germany-Frankfurt (2 slides), circa 1956 (Box SL8)
      - Germany--Hamburg, undated (Box SL8)
      - Greece (1 slide #261), undated (Box SL8)
      - India--Bangalore, undated (Box SL8)
      - India-Bombay (1 slide #174), undated (Box SL8)
      - India-Calcutta (1 slide #176A), undated (Box SL8)
      - India--Madras, undated (Box SL8)
      - India-Mgr's Office (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - India--New Delhi, undated (Box SL8)
      - Indonesia (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - Indonesia--Adforce, 1987 (Box SL8)
      - Italy-Milan (4 slides #130, 62), undated (Box SL8)
      - Italy-Rome (1 slide #141), undated (Box SL8)
      - Japan-Tokyo (19 slides), 1973 July (Box SL8)
      - Mexico (2 slides), 1973 July (Box SL8)
      - Netherlands-Amsterdam (1 slide), 1974 Apr. (Box SL8)
      - New Zealand--Wellington, undated (Box SL8)
      - Paraguay (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - Peru-Lima (4 slides), undated (Box SL8)
      - Philippines-Manila (2 slides #238, 191), undated (Box SL8)
      - Portugal-Lisbon (1 slide), undated (Box SL8)
      - Puerto Rico--San Juan (5 slides), circa 1974 and undated (Box SL8)
      - Singapore, undated (Box SL8)
      - South Africa--Johannesburg, undated (Box SL8)
      - Spain--Barcelona, undated (Box SL8)
      - Spain-Madrid (1 slide #83), undated (Box SL8)
      - Sri Lanka--Colombo, undated (Box SL8)
      - Sweden-Stockholm (3 slides), undated (Box SL8)
      - Switzerland-Zurich (5 slides), 1975 and undated (Box SL8)
      - Taiwan--Gaynor Associates, undated (Box SL8)
      - Taiwan--Taipei, undated (Box SL8)
      - Thailand--Bangkok, undated (Box SL8)
      - Turkey--Izmir, undated (Box SL8)
      - U.K.-London (6 slides), undated (Box SL8)
      - Uruguay--Montevideo, undated (Box SL8)
      - Venezuela--Caracas, undated (Box SL8)
  - People
    - Aciman, Eli, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Ad Age (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Allman, Jim, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Armstrong, Don (1 slide), 1960s (Box SL9)
    - Atkinson, Grace, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Azucar, Mario, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Balestrino, Chuck (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Ball, Jack (4 slides), 1970s (Box SL9)
    - Barnhill, John (1 slide), 1975 (Box SL9)
    - Barrington, Michael, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Bateman, David (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Bell, Fanny (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Berger, Ivan, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Bhatia, Amil, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Bjerne, Matts (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Black, George M. (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Branco, Hiran, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Bravo, Julian (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Brinwerhoff, John (3 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Brouillard, Joe (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Brouwet, Albert (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Brundage, Howard (3 slides), 1960s (Box SL9)
    - Bullmore, Jeremy (3 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Burns, Ron (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Calero, J.J. (1 slide), circa 1977 (Box SL9)
    - Campbell-Harris, David (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Camisa, Eugene (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Campion, Alfredo (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Carlton, William J. (5 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Carter, Jimmy (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Casseres, Amineta (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Castel-Branco, Joao Paulo (1 slide #139), undated (Box SL9)
    - Chiswell, John, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Chriswell, John (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Ciuti, Ezio, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Claravall, Tony (13 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Clark, Harry (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Clark, Jeff, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Cohen, Martin (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Colebrook, Miles, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Colwell, Robert (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Conn, Charles (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Connell, Hugh P. (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Constantinidis, Peter (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Cooper-Stevens, Cheryl (4 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Cooper-Evans, Michael (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Cronin, Jack (3 slides), circa 1980 (Box SL9)
    - Cruickshank, Bert (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Cunningham, Janet (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Daley, Kevin (5 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - de Angelo, Augusto (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - De Elexeru, Manuel, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Demogeot, Sylvie (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - De Smet, Frank, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Devine, Jack (2 slides), circa 1960s (Box SL9)
    - diez, Horacio, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Doyer (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Dunham,Peter (18 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Eashwar, Ganesh, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Elton, Wallace (20 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Evan, Mary Ellen (3 slides), 1984 (Box SL9)
    - Fenning, Andy, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Farrimond, Kelly, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Fickinger, Wayne (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Flower, Henry (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Figuerido, Eugenio (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Florida, John (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Frappier, Michel (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Friend, Charles (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Gaynor, John (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Ghosal, Subhas (1 slide #268), undated (Box SL9)
    - Gilow, Peter (12 slides #6,8,9,10,11,12,13,15,16,19,20,22), undated (Box SL9)
    - Godino, Rodolfo, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Gilson, Edith (2 slides), 1984 (Box SL9)
    - Glah,Roy (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Golfari, Marcos, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Gridley, Peter (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Guelfi, W., 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Guharoy, Debnath, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Haggarty, Clare (5 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Hall, David (2 slides #11,21), undated (Box SL9)
    - Haluk-Cansin, Izmir, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Hanly, Patrick (16 slides #3,4,5,6,8,9,10,11,13,14,16,17,19,20,unnumbered), undated (Box SL9)
    - Hebert, Jacques, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Henderson, Howard (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Hinks, Kenneth (1 slide), circa 1940s (Box SL9)
    - Hontiveros, Leon (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Horak, Peter (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Howarth, Ross (1 slide #219), undated (Box SL9)
    - Hylan, William (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Irvine, Bob (6 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Irving, Robert, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Jackson, Ann (4 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Jennen, Bruce (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Johnson, Brian (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Johnston, Donald G. (37 slides), 1958-1984 and undated (Box SL9)
    - Joyce, Timothy (2 slides #17,22), undated (Box SL9)
    - Kadaffi (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Kang, Sungman (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Karunaratne, Maurice (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Kestell, Paul, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Khanno, Mike, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - King, Margaret (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Kinney, Gil (3 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Kostyra, Richard (1 slide), 1977 (Box SL9)
    - Kovas, Ron (2 slides), 1978 (Box SL9)
    - Krupski, Andy (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Lanigan, Dennis (2 slides), 1978 and undated (Box SL9)
    - Leal, Roberto, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - Lindesay-Bethune, John (15 slides #2,5,9,10,11,12,13,14,16,17,18,19,21,22), 1970s (Box SL9)
    - Little, Lyde K. (14 slides #2,3,5,6,7,8,10,11,12,13,14,16,19), undated (Box SL9)
    - Macedo, Richard (1 slide #44), undated (Box SL9)
    - Maher, John (1 slide), 1977 (Box SL9)
    - McIntee, Stan (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Markman, Ken (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Marsland, Peter (2 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - Marti-Coll, Enrique (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Martin, Rodolfo (1 slide), undated (Box SL9)
    - Martinelli, Cesare, 1980s (Box SL9)
    - May, Mark (19 slides), undated (Box SL9)
    - McManis, Ralph, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Meek, Sam (13 slides), 1920s-1960s and undated (Box SL10)
    - Mesirow, Lorraine (4 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Mills, Peter (1 slide # 319), undated (Box SL10)
    - Miolán, Rafael (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Mitra, Ashish, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Monsarrat, John (1 slide), 1960s (Box SL10)
    - Nair, Niko (1 slide #303), undated (Box SL10)
    - Nehru, Nikhil, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Nicoll, Augusta (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Norsworthy, Bob (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Novotny (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - O'Brien, Wally (4 slides), 1984 (Box SL10)
    - O'Donnell, Joe (16 slides), 1982-1986 and undated (Box SL10)
    - O'Meara, Walter (1 slide #307), 1930 (Box SL10)
    - Olshan, Larry (3 slides), 1980 (Box SL10)
    - Orsi, Jose, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Ouseley, Robert (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Otero, Fernando (1 slide #201), undated (Box SL10)
    - Owett, Bernie (5 slides #1-5), 1970-1979 (Box SL10)
    - Parker, Austin (13 slides #1,2,3,5,6,7,10,11,12,13,16,17,18), undated (Box SL10)
    - Parrild, Sven (21 slides), 1972 (Box SL10)
    - Pavao, Lee (1 slide), 1977 (Box SL10)
    - Peniche, Bill, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Peters, Jack (4 slides #8,13,14,18), undated (Box SL10)
    - Peterson, Burt (1 slide #75), undated (Box SL10)
    - Platt, Lucille (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Plusker, Ellen (3 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Pollack, Jim (1 slide #35), undated (Box SL10)
    - Preschel, Lee (1 slide #23), undated (Box SL10)
    - Raymond, Charles (2 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Raymond, Jack (4 slides #25,31,33,37), undated (Box SL10)
    - Reber, John U. (5 slides), circa 1927-1930 and undated (Box SL10)
    - Resor, Helen (7 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Resor, Stanley (7 slides), 1930 (Box SL10)
    - Restall, Robin (2 slides #58, 231), undated (Box SL10)
    - Rigg, N., 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Robertson, Don (1 slide), 1978 (Box SL10)
    - Ross, Bill (3 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Rudolf, Peter (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Russell, T. Hamilton (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Schacte, Henry (3 slides), 1960s (Box SL10)
    - Schulte, Joe (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Scotti, A., 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Seymour, Dan (32 slides), circa 1960-1970 and undated (Box SL10)
    - Sherman, Ron (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Siebel (2 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Simonin, Dominique (15 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Soskin, David (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Souhami (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Speller, Geoffrey, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Spivak, Helayne (4 slides), 1996 (Box SL10)
    - Stanton, Henry (2 slides), 1949 (Box SL10)
    - Steveus, Henry (1 slide), 1950 (Box SL10)
    - Stephenson, Nancy (1 slide), 1947 (Box SL10)
    - Stouse, Norman (13 slides), 1955-1960s and undated (Box SL10)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Taylor,Gordon (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Tiggleman, Adriaan, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Thompson, J. Walter (24 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Thompson, Don (1 slide #24), undated (Box SL10)
    - Thompson, Walter (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Tiefenbrunner, Alfred (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Tienen (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Timur, Kenneth (Timmy) (2 slides), 1984 (Box SL10)
    - Treasure, John (18 slides #2,4,6,7,8,11,12,15,16,17,19,21,24,25,28,29,30,36), undated (Box SL10)
    - Troux, Denis, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Vainio, Ville, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Von Stom, Andre (12 slides #3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,13,14), undated (Box SL10)
    - Verner-Carlson, Hakan (2 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Value, Rudy (1 slide), 1927-1930 (Box SL10)
    - Waldo, Ruth (3 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Walker, Neil (16 slides #1,2,3,4,5,9,10,11,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,21), undated (Box SL10)
    - Watson, J.B. (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Webster, J.G.O. (5 slides), circa 1973 (Box SL10)
    - White, Bob (1 slide), circa 1960s (Box SL10)
    - White, Jeff, 1980s (Box SL10)
    - Wilson, Edward B. (4 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Wilson, Edward G. (5 slides), circa 1960s (Box SL10)
    - Yarnell, Timothy (15 slides #1,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,14,15,16,17,18,19), undated (Box SL10)
    - Young, James Webb (14 slides), 1919-1940s and undated (Box SL10)
  - Miscellaneous slides
    - Group Photographs
      - Corporate Retreat at Duke (49 slides), undated (Box SL10)
      - Doug Gordon, Ad Age (2 slides), undated (Box SL10)
      - L-R:J.W. Young, W. Elton, N.Strouse (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - L-R: William Hinks, E.G. Wilson, S. Meek (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - L-R: Salorio, Fitzpatrick (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Linda Fite, Thorn Wierum, Chris Ammon, Judy Fields (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Norman Strouse, Dan Seymour (2 slides), undated (Box SL10)
      - NY Review Board (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Review Board (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Wally O'Brien, Cathy Warga (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Unlabeled Group Shots (9 slides), 1986 and undated (Box SL10)
    - Logos and Publications
      - 125th Anniversary Publication (3 slides), undated (Box SL10)
      - 1887 Publication (2 slides), 1887 (Box SL10)
      - Baboon (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Blue Book (3 slides), 1909-10 (Box SL10)
      - Delineator (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Johnston Speech (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - JWT: The Largest Clinic of Adv. Exper. In the World (2 slides), 1945 (Box SL10)
      - JWT Logos (7 slides), 1887 and undated (Box SL10)
      - O.Wells (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - People (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Retail Shopping Areas- Map II (1 slide), 1927 (Box SL10)
      - Statue of Liberty (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - T-Square (3 slides), undated (Box SL10)
      - T-plan (In Spanish) (111 slides 1-111), 1972 (Box SL10)
      - Tall Ships (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
      - Unlabeled (7 slides), undated (Box SL10)
      - Women's College (1 slide), undated (Box SL10)
    - Other slides
      - Numbered #B1-B5, D1-D4, E1-E2,G1-G5 (16 slides), undated (Box SL10)
    - Slide Show--JWT History Presentation, circa 1989
      - Slide show, tray 1 (3 sheets), undated (Box SL11)
      - Slide show, tray 2 (2 sheets), undated (Box SL11)
      - Slide show, in-house version (2 sheets), undated (Box SL11)
      - Slide show, unidentified tray (2 sheets), undated (Box SL11)
      - Early publications, including slide of New Yorker cartoon, undated (Box SL11)
      - Loose slides (12 sheets), undated (Box SL11)
      - Printed version of slide show, Some Basic Roots of J. Walter Thompson Company, circa 1989, (3 folders) (Box SL12)
  - Microfiche1972-1991
    - Clients (black and white print--part 1) (3 folders), pre-1985 (Box SL13)
    - Clients (black and white print--part 2) (3 folders), pre-1985 (Box SL13)
    - Clients (color print) (4 folders), pre-1985 (Box SL13)
    - Clients (1 folder), 1989-1990 (Box SL13)
    - Clients (1 folder), 1990-1991 (Box SL13)
    - Clients (1 folder), 1991 (Box SL13)
    - Competitive agencies house advertisements (2 folders), undated (Box SL13)
    - New Business presentations (3 folders), 1977-1985 (Box SL13)
    - New Business presentations (3 folders), 1986-1990 (Box SL13)
- Thomas Veres Photographs and Negatives, 1963-1996 and undated, (60 boxes)
  Thomas Veres was a New York photographer under contract to JWT beginning in 1963. He photographed corporate events, staff, and other items. Many of his photographs were used to illustrate newsletter articles. Materials are segregated into Administrative Files (mainly paper records), Photographs and Negatives. Photographs and Negatives are organized according to Veres' job code, a three-part number identifying the quarter, year and job number. For example, a code 1-2-69 indicates job number 2 of the first quarter of 1969. Photographs taken prior to 1969 were received without job numbers and have been organized by year and therein alphabetically by subject.
  - Administrative Files,1969-1995 and undated
    - Articles,1969-1994 (Box TV1)
    - Award programs and literature,1977-1984 (Box TV1)
    - Billing and contract information,1970-1984, (3 folders) (Box TV1)
    - JWT events information,1977-1995 and undated, (2 folders) (Box TV1)
    - JWT publications,1970-1980 (Box TV1)
    - Maps and directions,undated (Box TV1)
    - Memoranda,1969-1995 (Box TV1)
    - Print orders and notes,1991-1995 and undated (Box TV1)
    - Miscellaneous,1977 and undated (Box TV1)
  - Photographs,1963-1996 and undated
    - No job number. 9th Floor Receptionists (Box TV2)
    - No job number. 11th Floor Receptionists (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Art exhibition II--Unidentified (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Basketball Team: team and action shots (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Baxter, Clayton, Rost (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Big Conference room Rebuilding (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Blackhouse boutique (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Brasil Manager (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Calcutta Manager (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Direct Mail group (Box TV2)
    - No job number. East Harlem Children--Red Onion (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Ethikos Press Conference (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Ford group (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Ford Meeting Hotel commodore, group action shots (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Ford Motor Company: photographs of printed pages re. 1962 Ford, 1964 Ford (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Ford Showroom with cars and people 1965 Fords (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Forum group (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Fran Wood: Debbie______Miss America studio and ______village, China Tour (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Frozen Food group lunch (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Fordam (sic) University and JWT (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Girls' exercise story (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Girls' softball--Central Park (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Girls' softball trophy (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Group in Board of Directors room, Denmark-Sutton, Mr. Parild (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Henry Wood, Tom Fucigna (Box TV2)
    - No job number. Hotel Roosevelt retiring man and secretary (Box TV2)